giantgummybears.com 2013-09-29

# Giant Gummy Bears!™ - Privacy Policy

| 

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

**What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: \- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) \- To help us improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) \- To administer things such as promotions and surveys 

**How do we protect your information?**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) does not get stored. 

**Do we use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**   
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Terms and Conditions**   
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://giantgummybears.com/return-policy.aspx>

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on January 1, 2013 

**Contacting Us**   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. [http://www.giantgummybears.com/contact-us.aspx](http://giantgummybears.com/contact-us.aspx)

|
